foodandhome.com 2011-05-16

# Privacy Policy | foodandhome.com

#### foodandhome.com Privacy Policy

foodandhome.com respects your privacy and is committed to protecting your personal information. We will only collect information we need to fulfill your requests and our legitimate business objectives. This privacy policy applies to your information that we collect and receive; it does not apply to practices of businesses that we do not own or control or people we do not employ. We will not send you marketing materials without your consent and at no time will we sell your information or release your personally-identifiable data without your permission. You can visit this Website without revealing who you are or providing any personal information about yourself. If we change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page or other places so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. 

By using this Website, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. Please read the following to understand how your personal information will be treated as you use our services. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices. 

This Website contains links to other online sites. These include links to resources in related topics and third-party websites that offer other related products. If you visit another website through a link on our Website, please consult the privacy policy of the website you are visiting. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other websites that you may visit. 

**Browsing the Website**  
If you browse through the Website without entering any personal data, we will gather and store certain information about your visit. This information does not identify you personally and cannot be linked back to you unless you decide at some point to identify yourself. If you are only browsing, we collect the following information: IP address, the type of browser and operating system used to access our Website, the date and time you access our Website, the pages you visit (click-through), and if you linked to our Website from another website, the address of that website as well as additional information related to your visit. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer the Website. 

**Information Collected**  
We collect the email addresses of consumers who communicate with us or through our authorized vendors via email. Any information provided by consumers becomes our property once received by us and may be used and disclosed as permitted in this Privacy Policy. 

We may share your personal information with our affiliated companies in order to identify products or services in which you may have interest, to improve our user experience and generally to engage in market research and for other internal business purposes. We may also aggregate your personal information with others' information and prepare reports on Website usage, purchase history or other factors for sale or distribution to others. Those reports are aggregated and include no personally identifying information. Finally, we may use your personal information to send you email or postal communications regarding products or services offered by us or by third parties with whom we have relationships in which we think you may be interested. We do not share, sell, trade or rent your personal information to third parties for unknown reasons. You may at any time choose not to receive promotional emails from us by contacting us at [support@kendallsquare.com](mailto:support@kendallsquare.com). Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may continue to contact you for the purpose of communicating information relating to this Website, as well as to facilitate, complete, or confirm any transaction that you may enter into or responding to your inquiry or request. 

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [support@kendallsquare.com](mailto:support@kendallsquare.com). 

**Use of Forums**  
If you choose to transmit, submit or post information through the Website's chat rooms, bulletin boards or other forums (the "Forums"), we will collect that information you provide. We retain this information as necessary to resolve disputes, provide customer support and troubleshoot problems as permitted by law and pursuant to our Terms of Use Agreement. 

**Cookies**  
We may place "cookies" on your personal computer. "Cookies" are small identifiers sent from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive, similar to a license plate, that help us to recognize you if you visit our Website again. Also, our Website uses cookies to track how you found our Website. Cookies are not designed to be used to get data from your hard drive, your e-mail or any other personal data about you. To protect your privacy, we do not use cookies to store or transmit any personal information about you on the Internet. You can reject cookies by changing your browser settings. Please note, however, that if you reject our cookies, it is possible that some web pages may not properly load, your access to certain information might be denied or you might have to enter information about yourself more than once. 

**Security**  
This Website has reasonable security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. 

**Third Party Advertising**  
We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies use non-personally identifiable information regarding your visit to this Website and other websites, such as the user IP address, pages viewed, date and time of your visit, and number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other personal information), to serve ads to you on this Website and other websites that may be of interest to you. In the course of serving advertisements to this Website, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.
